Curriculum vitae



PERSONAL INFORMATION

Name : Lee Chia-An, 李家安 Age : 24

Email : sz110010@gmail.com Phone : (+886)905 690 190

Language : Chinese, English Website : https://calee.xyz

EXPERIENCE

ORGANIZATION	DATE	TITLE	JOBS
TEDxNCTU 2017	2017/05 ~ 2018/05	IT Manager	IT infrastructure for the stage, network, and website
NCHC	2017/07 ~ 2017/12	Intern	Work on blockchain study. Research in Ethereum and smart contract
NCTU	2017/07 ~ 2017/08	TA	TA of the course, NCTU Scratch and Python, 2017 Summer
NCTU CSCC	2017/9 ~ 2019/9	Leader of Network Team	Managing the network of CS De- partment, monitoring and de- velop new networking features
NCHC	2018/07 ~ 2018/12	Intern	Develop a lightweight GPU com- puting platform. Based on the docker container environment
NCTU	2018/09 ~ 2019/01	TA	TA of the course, Network Plan- ning and Management Practices
NCTU	2020/03 ~ 2021/06	TA	TA of the course, <u>Wireless Networks</u>
NCTU CSLab	2019/9 ~	Master Student	5G core network development, Major in UPF-C and infrastructure

BIOGRAPHY

Chia-An, Lee is a master's student at National Chiao Tung University (NCTU) major in Computer Science at WIRELab, led by Prof. Jyh-Cheng Chen. Lee is currently developing the open-source core network free5GC.

He used to be a Teacher Assistant (TA) in NCTU Computer Science, Computer Center (CSCC). He is interested in IT, SRE, and Networking. Lee is also familiar with traditional networking and server management.

He has experienced in blockchain, Ethereum study, and IT infrastructure development during his internship at NCHC, Nation Center for High-performance Computing.

EDUCATION

SCHOOL	MAJOR	DEGREE	DATE
National Chiao Tung University	Department of Computer Science	Bachelor	2015/9 ~ 2019/6
National Yang Ming Chiao Tung University	Institute of Net- work Engineering	Master	2019/6 ~

SKILL

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGE	C/C++, Go, Python, Shell script	
PROFESSIONAL SKILL	Linux, Networking, Container, Infrastructure, OS	

PUBLICATIONS & PROJECTS

PUBLICATIONS / PROJECTS	DATE	DETAILS
Explore CVE-2017-9993 FFmpeg arbitrary file read vulnerability	2017/10	Oral presentation on TDOH Conf 2017 for introducing how to use CVE-2017-9993 to produce SSRF vulnerability
Implementation of lightweight GPU cloud computing AI platform	2018/10	Based on the docker container environment, implementing a cloud computing platform that performs AI computing on a GPU device.
NCTU CSCC Intranet Infrastructure	2018	Developing the intranet infrastructure for NCTU CSCC. Including Internet OSPF, NAT, firewall, DMZ, intranet design.